35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-11: Golf, circa 1954; slide 12-14: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (North Pole), 1957; slide 15-16: Marco Polo painting at Capital Cities Corporation, circa 1971; slide 17: Nepal (Lowell Thomas on elephant), 1957; slide 18: New Guinea, undated; s
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Marco Polo painting at Capital Cities Corporation, circa 1971, painting of a man holding up a pineapple in front of a throne], 16
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Nepal (Lowell Thomas on elephant), 1957, Lowell Thomas and two other men riding on an elephant], 17
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Poster promoting Lowell Thomas on WMT radio, 1951 (from Vern Hanson), "North East West SouthNews from everywhere by radio's distinguished reporter Lowell ThomasMonday-Friday 5:45pm Sponsored by P&G Ivory... WMT dial 600], 18
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: New Guinea, undated, elderly man with long white beard], 19
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Doctor Gordon Powell, Reverand Graham, Governor of New South Wales and lady sending a salute to Lowell Thomas, circa 1963], 20
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-2: Earl Thacker and Lowell Thomas, circa 1970; slide 3-8: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 10 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Earl Thacker and Lowell Thomas, circa 1970], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Earl Thacker and Lowell Thomas with two women, circa 1970], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Erling Strom (painting), undated], 8
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-15: Christl Thalhammer], circa 1963 - 1964; 11 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas with Cristl Thalhammer and a tribal man], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: painting of Cristl Thalhammer skiing in the mountains], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas and Cristl Thalhammer standing in front of a plane], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas and Cristl Thalhammer standing in front of a plane], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Residence of Cristl Thalhammer (?)], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Town where Cristl Thalhammer resides (?)], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Residence of Cristl Thalhammer (?)], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: busy street], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer petting a camel], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer petting a camel], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer riding on a camel in Egypt], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer sitting on a camel in Egypt with Lowell Thomas behind her], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas with Cristl Thalhammer, who is sitting on a camel, in Egypt], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer riding a camel in front of a pyramid in Egypt], 14
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas standing next to Cristl Thalhammer, who is sitting on a camel, in Egypt], 15
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-15: Christl Thalhammer], circa 1963 - 1964; 12 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer riding a camel by a pyramid in Egypt], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas standing next to Cristl Thalhammer as she sits on a camel in Egypt], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas standing next to Cristl Thalhammer, who is sitting on a camel, in Egypt], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas and Cristl Thalhammer with a camel in Egypt], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer riding a camel by a pyramid in Egypt], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Lowell Thomas and Cristl Thalhammer with a camel in Egypt], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; stairs leading up to ancient ruins], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; stairs leading up to ruins], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; ruins of an ancient building], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; ruins of an ancient archway], 10
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; stairs leading up to ancient ruins], 11
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; Lowell Thomas standing in front of ancient ruins], 12
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer standing in front of ancient ruins], 13
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; soldiers marching through a town], 14
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; three men with feathers], 15
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-10: Christl Thalhammer], circa 1963 - 1964; 13 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; men riding in the back of a truck with feathers], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; men riding in the back of a truck with feathers], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; tribal men in traditional tribal dress], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; tribal men in traditional tribal dress], 4
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; tribal soldiers marching with spears], 5
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; tribal soldiers marching with spears], 6
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; tribal soldier in traditional dress], 7
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; tribal soldiers with painted faces], 8
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; crowd of tribal soldiers], 9
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: Cristl Thalhammer; corpse being carried by tribesmen], 10
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1: World War II (Chiang Kai-shek, Lowell Thomas, General Albert C. Wedemeyer)], circa 1940s; 14 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: World War II; Chiang Kai-shek, Lowell Thomas, & General Albert C. Wedmeyer], 1
  - Slides found with photographic prints: [slide 1-4: Tibet (Dalai Lama)], 1949; 15 (Box 1592)
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 1
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 2
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 3
    - [Slides found with photographic prints: The Dalai Lama in Tibet], 4